== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Raj:)Why do you need Kripke?
(Raj:)Can't you just go to
Party City for helium?
(Leonard:)We'd have to go to every
Party City in California.
(Howard:)Sounds like you
on Cinco de Mayo.
(Raj:)Hey, people were still
talking about that party
on siete de Mayo.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, if that
Swedish team beats us,
(Sheldon:)I will never be able to enjoy
(Sheldon:)anything from
their country again.
(Sheldon:)Which is a shame,
because Swedish meatballs
are my favorite
toothpick-delivered meatball.
(Howard:)If you need liquid helium
so bad, I know a guy
(Howard:)who can get you some, if you
don't ask too many questions.
(Leonard:)Who is he?
Where does he work?
(Leonard:)How does he
get the helium?
(Sheldon:)How many questions
are too many questions?
(Howard:)Maybe he's not for you.
(Sheldon:)Four questions.
There answer's four.
(Bernadette:)Hey, you know
who went out
(Bernadette:)on a date the other
night? Stuart.
(Penny:)Oh, good for him.
(Bernadette:)I thought so, too.
(Penny:)So is she, like, homeless,
or framing him for a crime?
(Bernadette:)He's using some kind
of dating app on his phone.